(Bernadette:)- Howard.
- No, that's okay, Bernadette.
(Penny:)Sometimes these things
just don't work out.
Yeah. It's all good. We'll always
have feelings for each other.
(Bernadette:)Oh. That's nice.
See? She knew what "always" meant.
(Penny:)Wow, you're like a dog with a bone,
aren't you?
- I'm just making a point.
- ls the point you don't know...
(Penny:)- ...when to let something go?
- People, people, please.
(Sheldon:)Before you say something
you both regret...
(Sheldon:)...I'd like to place my order.
Yeah, hang on, Sheldon.
You know why we can't be together?
(Penny:)- Because you always have to be right.
- That is not true.
I gotta go with Leonard on this.
He is wrong more than anyone I know.
You know what, I just realized
I'm on a break. I'll get someone else.
(Sheldon:)Promise me
when our new waitress comes over...
(Sheldon:)...you will not start a complicated,
on-again, off-again relationship with her.
Because I'm very very hungry.